data = [
    {"question": "The Axolotl is an amphibian that can spend its whole life in a larval state.",
     "correct_answer": "True"},
    {"question": "The name of the main character of the video game &quot;The Legend of Zelda&quot;, is Zelda.",
     "correct_answer": "False"},
    {
        "question": "Matt Damon played an astronaut stranded on an extraterrestrial planet in both of the movies"
                    " Interstellar and The Martian.",
        "correct_answer": "True"},
    {"question": "In &quot;Super Mario 64&quot;, collecting 100 coins on a level will give you a 1-UP.",
     "correct_answer": "False"},
    {
        "question": "There was a satirical candidate named &quot;Deez Nuts&quot; running in the 2016 US presidential"
                    " elections.",
        "correct_answer": "True"},
    {"question": "Alaska is the largest state in the United States.",
     "correct_answer": "True"},
    {"question": "Nutella is produced by the German company Ferrero.",
     "correct_answer": "False"},
    {"question": "The &#039;Squaring the Circle&#039; problem is solvable.",
     "correct_answer": "False"},
    {"question": "The United States was a member of the League of Nations.",
     "correct_answer": "False"},
    {"question": "A scientific study on peanuts in bars found traces of over 100 unique specimens of urine.",
     "correct_answer": "False"},
    {"question": "According to Greek Mythology, Zeus can control lightning.",
     "correct_answer": "True"},
]
